Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative files, 1952-1983; MS2061 Series 2
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 1206)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 1207)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 1208)
  - Public Relations Subscription, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 1209)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 1210)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 1211)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1965-1966 (Box 82, Folder 1212)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1213)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1214)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1215)
  - Public Relations Staff Communication, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 1216)
  - Public Relations Promotion Oct.-Feb., 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1217)
  - Public Relations Promotion Mar.-Sept. (folder 1), 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1218)
  - Public Relations Promotion Mar.-Sept. (folder 2), 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1219)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1220)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Automation, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1221)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1222)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1223)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1224)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1225)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1226)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1227)
  - Public Relations Staff Communication, 1967-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1228)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1229)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Oct.-July, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1230)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Aug.-Sept., 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1231)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1232)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1233)
  - Public Relations Staff Communication, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1234)
  - Public Relations Promotion Oct.-Apr., 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1235)
  - Public Relations Promotion May-Aug., 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1236)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Oct.-Apr., 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1237)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions May-Aug., 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1238)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Daily Records, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1239)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Batch & Correction Sheets, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1240)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1241)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1970 September 18-1971 September 11 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #1245
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1971 April 19-August 31 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #1246
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1970 September 08-1971 February 17 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #1247
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1971 March 03-May 04 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder # 1248
  - Public Relations Subscriptions, 1971 April 08-August 31 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #1249
  - Public Relations Subscriptions - 1970-71 Daily Records, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #1250
  - Public Relations Subscriptions - 1970-71 Batch & Corrections Sheets - Sept.-June, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #1251
  - Public Relations Subscriptions - 1970-71 - Batch & Correction Sheets - July-Aug., 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #1252
  - Public Relations Subscriptions - 1970-71 - Phone Campaign, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations Box Office-1970-71, 1970 August 05-1971 January 12 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #1254
  - Public Relations Correspondence - 1970-71, 1970 September 19-1971 July 14 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #1255
  - Public Relations Staff Communication-1970-71, 1970 February 12-1971 August 16 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #1256
  - Public Relations Promotion-1971-72 Sept.-Mar., 1971 September 01-1972 December 17 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #1257
  - Public Relations Promotion-1971-72 Sept.-Mar., 1971 December 24-1972 February 24 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #1258
  - Public Relations Promotion-1971-72 Apr.-Aug., 1972 April 04-August 23 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #1259
  - Public Relations Subscriptions-1971-72 Sept.-Apr, 1971 September 07-1972 September 25 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #1260
  - Public Relations Subscriptions-1971-72 May-Aug., 1972 June 02-August 04 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #1261
  - Public Relations Subscriptions-1971-72 Daily Record, 1971-1972 August 31 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #1262
  - Public relations Subscriptions-1971-72 Batch and Correction Sheets Sept.-May, 1971 September 03-1972 May 31 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #1263
  - Public Relations Subscriptions - 1971-72 Batch and Correction Sheets June-Aug., 1971 June 01-1972 August 31 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder #1264
  - Public Relations Box Office - 1971-72, 1972 May 31-August 04 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #1265
  - Public Relations Correspondence - 1971-72, 1971 September 15-1972 August 15 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #1266
  - Public Relations Staff Communication - 1971-72, 1971 September 08-1972 August 24 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #1267
  - Public Relations Promotion - 1971-73, 1971 September 08-1973 November 28 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #1268
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Sept.-May, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 1269)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions June - Aug., 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 1270)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Daily Records, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 1271)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions Batch & Correction Sheets, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 1272)
  - Public Relations Box Office, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 1273)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 1274)
  - Public Relations Staff Communication, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 1275)
  - Public Relations Promotion, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1276)
  - Public Relations Subscriptions (folder 1), 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1277)
  - . Box Office (Jacques Brel), 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1278)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1279)
  - Subscription Master Records Abraham - Berman, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1280)
  - Subscription Master Records Bernstein - Byers, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1281)
  - Subscription Master Records Cable - Duvinage, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1282)
  - Subscription Master Records Eaffy - Fuller, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1283)
  - Subscription Master Records Gage - Guttman, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1284)
  - Subscription Master Records Haas - Irwin, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1285)
  - Subscription Master Records Jeanes - Kroopnick, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1286)
  - Subscription Master Records Lake - Lewis, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1287)
  - Subscription Master Records Malden - Stanchfield, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1288)
  - Subscription Master Records Steck - Tyrrell, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1289)
  - Subscription Master Records Udelson - Weeb, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1290)
  - Subscription Master Records Webster - Zlotnick, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1291)
  - Subscription Master Records Anglin - Appleton, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1292)
  - Subscription Master Records Aptaker - Barth, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1293)
  - Subscription Master Records Barthelmes - Bernstein, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1294)
  - Subscription Master Records Berreckman - Bradford, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1295)
  - Subscription Master Records Branch - Butler, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1296)
  - Subscription Master Records Buttrick - Cunningham, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1297)
  - Subscription Master Records Currie - DeWilde, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1298)
  - Subscription Master Records Dickenson - Eng, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1299)
  - Subscription Master Records Engel - Fineman, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1300)
  - Subscription Master Records Fink - Friedgut, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1301)
  - Subscription Master Records Friedman - Glowacki, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1302)
  - Subscription Master Records Godfrey - Grest, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1303)
  - Subscription Master Records Griffin - Harwood, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1304)
  - Subscription Master Records Hauptman - Hnatysh, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1305)
  - Subscription Master Records Hoard - Iwamoto, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1306)
  - Subscription Master Records Jackson - Johnson, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1307)
  - Subscription Master Records Johnston - Kent, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1308)
  - Subscription Master Records Kibler - Lieb, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1309)
  - Subscription Master Records Liebenberg - Mantel, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1310)
  - Subscription Master Records Mantell - Mazor, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1311)
  - Subscription Master Records Mazur - Mercer, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1312)
  - Subscription Master Records Mestel - Monte, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1313)
  - Subscription Master Records Montgomery - Neilan, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1314)
  - Subscription Master Records Nejelski - Oliver, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1315)
  - Subscription Master Records Olson - Pauker, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1316)
  - Subscription Master Records Paul - Pollack, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1317)
  - Subscription Master Records Pollak - Rall, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1318)
  - Subscription Master Records Ramirez - Ritt, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1319)
  - Subscription Master Records Ritter - Rosenfeld, 1970-1971 (Box 105, Folder 1320)
  - Subscription Master Records Rosenthal - Ruef, 1970-1971 (Box 105, Folder 1321)
  - Subscription Master Records Rund - Scheips, 1970-1971 (Box 105, Folder 1322)
  - Subscription Master Records Schenker - Sparrow, 1970-1971 (Box 105, Folder 1323)
  - Subscription Master Records Simmons - Shelburne, 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1324)
  - Subscription Master Records Shelfo - Slosberg, 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1325)
  - Subscription Master Records Sloss - Stern, 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1326)
  - Subscription Master Records Sternfeld - Thompson, 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1327)
  - Subscription Master Records Thornton - Vaughn, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 1328)
  - Subscription Master Records Van Zandf - Weincek, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 1329)
  - Subscription Master Records Weinstein - Wolfe, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 1330)
  - Subscription Master Records Wolff - Zwerdling, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 1331)
  - Subscription Printouts, 1971 April 21 (Box 108, Folder 1332)
  - Subscription Printouts, 1971 April 21 (Box 109, Folder 1333)
  - Subscription Printouts, 1972 April 01 (Box 110, Folder 1334)
  - Subscription Printouts, 1972 April 01 (Box 111, Folder 1335)
  - Subscription Applications, 1961-1970 (Box 112, Folder 1336)
  - Subscription Applications Unfinished, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 1337)
  - Subscription Applications NA, 1971 June 29 (Box 112, Folder 1338)
  - Subscription Applications Designated A, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 1339)
  - Subscription Applications NO, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 1340)
  - Subscription Applications 1, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 1341)
  - Subscription Applications 2, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1342)
  - Subscription Applications 3, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1343)
  - Subscription Applications 4, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1344)
  - Funding Foundation Donation-Records, 1964-1969 (Box 114, Folder 1345)
  - Funding Eugene and Agnes Meyer Foundation, 1964-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1346)
  - Funding Mary Roberts Rhinehart Foundation, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1347)
  - Funding Philip M. Stern Family Fund Matching Grant, 1965-1971 (Box 114, Folder 1348)
  - Funding William C. Whitney Foundation, 1965-1971 (Box 114, Folder 1349)
  - Funding National Endowment for the Arts, 1966-1974 (Box 114, Folder 1350)
  - Funding D.C. Commission on the Arts, 1968-1971 (Box 115, Folder 1351)
  - Funding Ford Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 115, Folder 1352)
  - Funding Hattie M. Strong Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 115, Folder 1353)
  - Funding Morris and Gwendolyn Cafritz Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 115, Folder 1354)
  - Funding Paul and Annette Himmelfarb Foundation, Inc., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 1355)
  - Funding Brookdale Foundation (participants and Issues: H. Martin Nemetz, Leonard Garment, Arnold Schwartz, Pat Nixon Theater, Pat Nixon Children's Cultural Center), 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 1356)
  - Funding Other Foundation Appeals, 1966-1972 (Box 115, Folder 1357)
  - Funding Contributions, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 1358)
  - Funding Contributions, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 1359)
  - Funding Contributions, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 1360)
  - Funding Fund Raising, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 1361)
  - Funding Contributions, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 1362)
  - Funding Capital Fund Drive 1, 1969-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1363)
  - Funding Capital Fund Drive 2, 1969-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1364)
  - Funding Capital Fund Drive 3, 1969-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1365)
  - Funding Fund Raising, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 1366)
  - Funding Contributions, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 1367)
  - Funding Fund Raising, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1368)
  - Funding Contributions, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1369)
  - Funding Fund Raising, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 1370)
  - Funding Contributions, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 1371)
  - Funding Fund Raising, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 1372)
  - Funding Contributions, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 1373)
  - Actors Equity, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 1374)
  - Actors Equity, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 1375)
  - Actors Equity, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 1376)
  - Actors Equity, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 1377)
  - Actors Equity, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 1378)
  - Actors Equity, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 1379)
  - Actors Equity, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 1380)
  - Actors Equity, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 1381)
  - Actors Equity, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 1382)
  - Actors Equity, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1383)
  - Actors Equity, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 1384)
  - Actors Equity, Jan.-June, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 1385)
  - Actors Equity, July-Dec., 1970 (Box 119, Folder 1386)
  - Actors Equity, Jan.-Mar., 1971 (Box 119, Folder 1387)
  - Actors Equity, Apr.-June, 1971 (Box 120, Folder 1388)
  - Actors Equity, July-Sept., 1971 (Box 120, Folder 1389)
  - Actors Equity, Oct.-Dec., 1971 (Box 120, Folder 1390)
  - Actors Equity, Jan.-Mar., 1972 (Box 120, Folder 1391)
  - Actors Equity, Apr.-June, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1392)
  - Actors Equity, July-Sept., 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1393)
  - Actors Equity, Oct.-Dec., 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1394)
  - Actors Equity, Jan.-Mar., 1973 (Box 122, Folder 1395)
  - Actors Equity, Apr.-Dec., 1973 (Box 122, Folder 1396)
  - Actors Equity, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 1397)
  - American Federation of Television & Radio Artists, 1966-1972 (Box 122, Folder 1398)
  - D.C. Federation of Musicians, 1970-1973 (Box 122, Folder 1399)
  - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 1400)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1966 (Box 122, Folder 1401)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1967-1968 (Box 122, Folder 1402)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1403)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 1404)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1405)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1406)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 1407)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1408)
  - Voice of America Latin Division, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 1409)
  - Associations and Conferences American Association of University Women, 1966 (Box 124, Folder 1410)
  - Associations and Conferences Associated Councils of the Arts, 1966-1972 (Box 124, Folder 1411)
  - Associations and Conferences United Performing Arts of Washington, 1966-1972 (Box 124, Folder 1412)
  - Associations and Conferences Theatre Communications Group, 1967-1973 (Box 124, Folder 1413)
  - Associations and Conferences International Exchange, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 1414)
  - Associations and Conferences National Playwrights Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 124, Folder 1415)
  - Associations and Conferences Task Force on the Performing Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 124, Folder 1416)
  - Associations and Conferences American Society of Theatre Arts, 1971-1973 (Box 124, Folder 1417)
  - Associations and Conferences Fourth International Congress of the Association Internationale du Theatre pour L'Enfance et la Jeunesse, 1972 (Box 124, Folder 1418)
  - Associations and Conferences Virginia Theatre Conference, 1972 October 07 (Box 124, Folder 1419)
  - Associations and Conferences American Women Playwrights Association, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 1420)
  - Royalties, Production 1, The Matchmaker, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1421)
  - Royalties, Production 2, A Hatful of Rain, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1422)
  - Royalties, Production 3, The Lesson & The Chairs, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1423)
  - Royalties, Production 4, A Clearing in the Woods, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1424)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1425)
  - Royalties, Production 5, Cry of the Raindrop, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1426)
  - Royalties, Production 6, Tevya and His Daughters, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1427)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 1428)
  - Royalties, Production 8, A Country Scandal, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1429)
  - Royalties, Production 9, Legend of Sarah, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1430)
  - Royalties, Production 10, The Glass Menagerie, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1431)
  - Royalties, Production 11, Three at 8:30, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1432)
  - Royalties, Production 12, Period of Ad'ustment, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1433)
  - Royalties, Production 13, The Establishment, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1434)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 1435)
  - Royalties, Production 14, Brecht on Brecht, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 1436)
  - Royalties, Non-Equity Production 1, The Winter Peach, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 1437)
  - Royalties, Non-Equity Production 2, Miss Amurica, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 1438)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 1439)
  - Royalties, Non-Equity Production 4, Zoo Story & The Sandbox & Waiting for Godot & The Dumbwaiter & The Collection, 1964 (Box 125, Folder 1440)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1964 (Box 125, Folder 1441)
  - Royalties, Production 21, A Touch of the Poet, 1965 (Box 125, Folder 1442)
  - Royalties, Production 23, Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, 1965 (Box 125, Folder 1443)
  - Royalties, Production 24, U.S.A., 1965 (Box 125, Folder 1444)
  - Royalties, Production 25, Earnest in Love, 1965 (Box 125, Folder 1445)
  - Royalties, Production 26, Romeo and Jeannette, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1446)
  - Royalties, Production 27, The Typist & The Tiger, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1447)
  - Royalties, Production 29, Eccentricities of a Nightingale, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1448)
  - Royalties, Production 30, Spread Eagle, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1449)
  - Royalties, Production 31, The Knack, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1450)
  - Production 32, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1451)
  - Royalties, Production 33, The Fantasticks, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1452)
  - Royalties, Children's Theater Production7, Bremen Town Musicians, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 1453)
  - Royalties, Children's Theater Production9, Lady Precious Stream, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 1454)
  - Royalties, Children's Theater Production 10, Absolutel Time, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 1455)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 1456)
  - Royalties, Production 34, Tiny Alice, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1457)
  - Royalties, Production 35, The Marriage of Mr. Mississippi, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1458)
  - Royalties, Production 36, The Killer, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1459)
  - Royalties, Production 37, Waters of Babylon, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1460)
  - Royalties, Production 38, Son of Spread Eagle, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1461)
  - Royalties, Production 39, Luv, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1462)
  - Royalties, Production 40, My Sweet Charlie, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1463)
  - Royalties, Production 41, Eh?, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1464)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading Pagoda 1, Death of Morris Biederman & By the Old Moulmein, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1465)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1466)
  - Royalties, Production 42, No Man's Land, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1467)
  - Royalties, Production 43, Caligula, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1468)
  - Royalties, Production 44, Five Evenings, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1469)
  - Royalties, Production 45, Green Julia, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1470)
  - Royalties, Production 46, Spread Eagle Strikes Back, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1471)
  - Royalties, Production 47, The Gingham Dog, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1472)
  - Royalties, Production 48, The Lion in Winter, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1473)
  - Royalties, Production 49, Lock Up Your Daughters, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1474)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 5, The Scene, Please, Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones-, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1475)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 6, And Other Caged Birds & Willyum, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1476)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1477)
  - Royalties, Production 50, Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1478)
  - Royalties, Production 51, Who's Happy Now?, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1479)
  - Royalties, Production 52,The Indian Wants the Bronx & And Other Caged Birds, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1480)
  - Royalties, Production 53, Bread and Butter, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1481)
  - Royalties, Production 54, Spread Eagle IV, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1482)
  - Royalties, Production 55, The Moths, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1483)
  - Royalties, Production 56, The Decline and Fall of the Entire World..., 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1484)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 7, Some Winter Games, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1485)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 10, The Note & The Production Room, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1486)
  - Royalties, Jazz 3, Marshall Hawkins Quintet, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1487)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1488)
  - Royalties, Production 57, The Wolves, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1489)
  - Royalties, Production 58, Adventures in the Skin Trade, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1490)
  - Royalties, Production 59, Serenading Louie, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1491)
  - Royalties, Production 60, Continental Divide, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1492)
  - Royalties, Production 61, Exit the King, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1493)
  - Royalties, Production 62, Before You Go, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1494)
  - Royalties, Production 63, Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1495)
  - Royalties, Production 64, The Last Sweet Days of Isaac, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1496)
  - Royalties, Production 65, A Fifth of Spread Eagle, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1497)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 14, Countess Frieda, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1498)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 15, Someone's Crying, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1499)
  - Royalties, Network Taping 2, Someone's Crying, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1500)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 1501)
  - Royalties, Production 66, Little Boxes, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1502)
  - Royalties, Production 67, The Web and The Rock, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1503)
  - Royalties, Production 68, The Chinese & Dr. Fish, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1504)
  - Royalties, Production 69, Father's Day, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1505)
  - Royalties, Production 70, Whores, Wars, and Tin Pan Alley, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1506)
  - Royalties, Production 71, Adaptation/Next, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1507)
  - Royalties, Production 72, All Over, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1508)